The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Lowly servant of this realm,
why are you causing trouble ?
This person
is not from this realm.
Who are you !?
How dare you disrespect Upper Celestial !?
Upper Celestial ?
You bunch of ignorant fools !
A Celestial is right before you,
yet you mistook an outsider for a Celestial ?
Outsider ?
Who ?
The one who protected our clan
is the Celestial !
I don't
acknowledge you !
Is that so ?
Kneel !
Wh...
What is this ?
Ta Shan !
You lowly slaves,
are bound by the slave imprint.
Yet you can't even recognize your own master ?
Slave imprint ?
The Forsaken Immortal Clan of Planet Suzaku
and the Chosen Immortal Clan here
are all bound by this imprint ?
The celestial decree says
that when we see a Celestial,
our hearts will be stirred with emotions
of natural reverence.
But the reason we cannot help
but be reverent
is this slave imprint...
Years ago, your clan's ancestors
were defeated by the Celestial Realm
and branded with the slave imprint.
Since then,
generation after generation,
you have all been slaves of my Celestial Realm.
This lowly one
pays respect to Upper Celestial.
I beg Upper Celestial
to spare the lives of my clansmen.
The aura of this thing
is disturbing.
These slaves didn't know the rules.
Forgive the embarrassment, fellow cultivator.
Let me punish them briefly
and I will respectfully send you off
to leave this place.
I'll give you celestial artifacts
as compensation.
You use this slave imprint to force us to kneel ?
But I...
will not kneel !
Ignorant fool.
Why ?
Why can the Celestial control the fog beasts ?
Why !?
Your whole purpose
was always to feed the fog beasts,
and there is no reason why.
I was wrong...
Ta Shan...
Grandpa was wrong.
Feeding us to the fog beasts ?
On what grounds !?
It's your fate,
you can't change it.
I, Ta Shan,
never believed in fate !
Grandpa !
I thought that
you were a smart one.
I wanted to spare your life.
Why do you insist on courting death ?
I'm just curious
on whether this butterfly is as the rumors said:
able to slay Celestials and Gods.
Very well,
since you care so much for these lowly slaves...
Stop.
The complete God Slaying Chariot
can indeed kill Celestials and Gods.
These words were no lie.
How is this possible !?
Stop him !
Stop.
What kind of artifact is this ?
We're saved !
That Celestial was destroyed !
If he truly were a Celestial,
he wouldn't go down that easily.
It was an avatar.
Blood Formation Space
Long Daozi
Rank 1 Sky Celestial
Nirvana Scryer
He could actually destroy my avatar ?
Never mind,
after 30 000 years,
this is the first time someone has broken in.
He does have some skill.
30 000 years...
30 000 years ago
Celestial Realm
Reporting to Celestial Emperor,
Long Daozi took advantage of the chaos
on the northern front to kill the Celestial Envoy Chen Cong
and steal his celestial artifact,
the Mirror of Mystical Light.
Please judge him, Celestial Emperor.
Chen Cong died in the melee,
what makes you say I killed him ?
Did you think that I
was deaf and blind on the battlefield ?
Emperor !
I...
I was merely foolish for an instant !
I took the celestial artifact
to gain inspiration
and better share Celestial Emperor's burdens !
Celestial Emperor, calm your anger !
Long Daozi's cave
Master !
My body...
The Celestial Emperor's spell, Call the Wind,
can never be expelled
once it enters your body.
Remember this in the future.
Never ever face that spell again.
Otherwise,
you'll die for sure.
Circulate this mantra with origin energy,
36 cycles per day.
After 10 000 years,
you may be able to reshape your body.
10 000 years !?
Master,
that's so long !
Long !?
Master has found a place for you to enter seclusion.
Have you ever heard of
the Nether Beast ?
This beast's belly holds
a self-contained world.
Master has trapped it in the Western Domain of Allheaven
and put it to sleep.
Although the Nether Beast is asleep,
it requires a massive amount of vitality.
For this,
I set up the Mysterious Yin Cauldron
inside its body
and ordered the Chosen Immortal Clan
to guard it for generations.
The Mysterious Yin Cauldron produces fog beasts
which hunt for themselves.
And feed the Nether Beast with resentment.
This endless cycle
sustains this beast
with unending vitality.
Within this beast's body,
you will be safe.
The reason Master went to such great lengths
must be more important than just saving me.
Correct.
Several thousands of years ago,
before I became a Celestial,
I had a son in the mortal world.
He died because of me.
I searched all four Celestial Realms
and found for him
the Heaven-Avoiding Coffin that can revive the dead and regrow bodies.
I originally planned to place him within that Nether Beast as well.
Now,
you will go together with him.
That Heaven-Avoiding Coffin may be questionable.
If my son's soul wasn't on the verge of dissipating,
I would never use it.
Disciple,
today's misfortune
is the result of your impatience for success
and your selfishness.
Don't repeat the same mistakes
in these 10 000 years of seclusion.
30 000 years...
I thought you were just a pile of dry bones.
I never expected that several hundred years ago,
Heaven-Avoiding Coffin
you would actually begin to breathe.
10 000 years !?
After 30 000 years,
and exhausting all my strength,
I only reformed this skeleton !
Master,
when you sent me here back then,
was it really for my sake
or to trap me
to guard the coffin for you ?
However,
that no longer matters.
I've endured too many boring days in here.
I hope that
he can entertain me a little.
This place is not good,
I can't stay any longer.
Ta Shan !
Clan Head,
he's beyond saving.
There is...
nothing we can do anymore.
Grandpa...
Grandpa was wrong.
Ta Shan, you were right.
Why didn't we rebel ?
We should have rebelled long ago !
Grandpa will take you away now.
I'll take you
far away from this place.
Ta Shan !
The backlash of the slave imprint
is burning his innards.
I have a way
that may save his life.
Really ?
But it will erase his emotions.
From then on, his mind will be asleep
and he will only obey my orders.
Do you mean
like a puppet ?
Then my grandson
will have a chance to awaken one day.
I will preserve his consciousness.
As for the rest,
it depends on his own fortune.
Even then,
I only have a 50% chance of success.
Do I save him ?
The choice is yours.
I...
am...
willing...
I said that
as long as you can lead my clan away from this place,
I would
serve you for life
without regard
for life or death.
Good.
I promise.
The ancestral skulls Senior Situ gave me
have actually come in handy.
The Chosen Immortal and Forsaken Immortal share the same origin.
If I use the ancestral skulls to refine him,
his Origin Soul will be protected,
and his body strengthened.
Refining a Celestial Guard
requires his consent.
If there is the slightest resistance,
it will fail for sure.
Heavenly Ghost,
condense !
Ta Shan...
Ta Shan !
He's not dead !
Ta Shan
Celestial Guard
Peak Corporeal Yang
Grandson !
Grandson,
you're alive.
You...
Ta Shan !
You're alive !
His soul is still in there.
One day,
he may awaken.
Thank you, Benefactor.
Time to leave.
It's all right.
Let's go.
An Ancient God artifact
is truly extraordinary.
Ta Shan !
Celestial Guards don't cultivate the Origin Soul.
These kinds of attacks
are useless against him.
Peak Corporeal Yang,
a step away from Nirvana Scryer.
Is this...
still my grandson ?
Once you step into this formation,
there is no turning back.
Ta Shan ?
It's him !
My grandson
is still in there...
Even if his Origin Soul is asleep,
his body still remembers his hatred.
It seems one day,
he may really awaken.
It's time
to face that Celestial.
This is...
Courting death ?
“The slave imprint is fused with the tattoos of the Chosen Immortal Clan members. This slave imprint is extremely overbearing and is far more powerful than the one used on Li Yuan’s family. After all, the one used on Li Yuan’s family only made his family serve one Celestial.”
---
“I’ll use the celestial jades to nourish your body, the heavenly ghost to help you form a soul, and the skulls of your ancestors to help you perfect your tattoos. Ta Shan, I’ll gift you a great fortune!”
[...]
“During each of my successful attempts at creating celestial guards, I integrated the heavenly ghost. I wonder if there is a connection. Could it be that including the heavenly ghost increases the chance of success?”
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
by a child's steadfast heart ?
Nascent Soul
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
stand in the way,
Soul Transformation
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
and ask this question to the sky.
Ascendant
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.